下一项是周五的校友会舞会
Next item is Friday's alumni dance.
进度如何
How's that progressing.
我给所有没蹲监狱和号子的校友
I've emailed every former student who's not in prison or jail,
都发了邮件  请注意其中的区别
everyone remember there's a difference.
我们的校友对此比较敏感
Our alumni are touchy about that.
有什么区别
What's the difference?
如果警察不喜欢你  你是蹲号子
You go to jail if a cop doesn't like you.
不知道你穷的情况下是不会让你去蹲监狱的
They can't send you to prison without knowing you're poor.
你能相信这里出去的  有一半从了政
Do you believe half our own politics?
是吧  是
Yeah.Yeah.
我还在找好DJ
I'm still trying to find a good DJ.
即我还在努力区分什么叫好DJ什么是坏DJ
By which I mean figure out what makes a DJ good, or bad,
手机和笔记本电脑比哪个好
or different from a phone or laptop.
昌  你给市政局会议准备的PPT
Chang, how's it going with the PowerPoint
搞得怎么样了
for the city council meeting?
好问题
Good question.
昌和PPT
失望之旅
当你问我是否会做PPT时
When you asked if I knew PowerPoint,
我回答  是
I said, yes.
是
但我其实是什么意思呢
What did I really mean?
逐年的是
不是  是
表里有是与不是
These are yeses and nos in the chart.
看起来似乎是一样的
They appear to be the same.
但是
However,
你会发现
I think you'll find.
要敲破蛋壳  才有真知
That within some eggs is the truth.
里面应该是一块钱纸币
That should have been a dollar bill.
但我不是魔术师
But I'm no magician.
我只是会做PPT的男人
I'm just a guy that knows PowerPoint.
好  会议继续
Okay, pushing that meeting.
其他方面  在全国高校地区  包括此地
In other news, campuses across the country including this area
都发现了游击营销在飞速增长
have been seeing a dramatic rise in guerilla marketing.
他们要市场干嘛  他自己就赞翻了
Why did they need marketing, they're amazing.
是游击  不是猩猩
That's guerrilla with a u.
懂了
Got it.
我指的是潜伏在人群中
I'm talking about undercover
隐秘地为某种商品
advertisers that blend in with the public
悄悄打广告的人
while covertly marketing certain products.
在你不知不觉中打广告
They can advertise things without you knowing?
这是不是犯法啊
Is that legal?
感觉像被洗脑了
It sounds like brain Windexing.
是合法的
It is legal.
几乎是无害的  但要保护好我们学校里
It's mostly harmless, but I would like to protect some of our
那些比较容易受影响的学生不被过度影响
more impressionable students from being unduly influenced.
所以谁发现了什么迹象  马上通知院长
So if you see anything let the Dean know.
好  都别慌啊
Okay, don't freak out.
有人跟我说本田刚刚上市了一款
Someone just told me that Honda has released some kinda
超级汽车  叫本田飞度
super vehicle called the Honda Fit.
小型车不张扬  可却能包罗万象
It's a small car with a big personality that can handle anything,
应对生活投向你的一切
life throws at you.
我还在这废什么话
Why am I standing here talking about it?
我要去找本田经销商  学校放假
I have to find a Honda dealer, school is cancelled.
本田飞度来了
The Honda Fit is happening.
它终于来了
It's finally happening.
我马上把学校资产小小冻结一下下
I'm just going to give this school's assets a quick freezy wheezy.
这会结束了吗
Is this meeting over?
差不多了吧  有时候我们只是闲聊会
I think so, but sometimes we just hang out and say funny stuff.
好好聊哈
Have fun with that.
同学们  你们绝不觉得埃尔罗伊
Guys, do you feel like Elroy doesn't like us
不像我们喜欢彼此那么喜欢我们
as much as we like him and each other?
他可能还不知道自己的角色定位
He probably doesn't know his role yet.
他到底是黑版皮尔斯
I mean, is he black Pierce,
还是老版特洛伊  还是雪瑞不背包
old Troy, or Shirley without a giant purse?
自从特洛伊走后
I haven't exactly been a whirlwind
我就没有真正开心过
of entertainment since Troy left.
才不是呢
That's not true.
不只是我  你们也一样无聊
It's not just me, you guys have been boring too.
好吧  我就问问
Okay. I just gotta ask.
这个特洛伊到底有什么特别的
What was so special about this Troy person?
他家产彩虹啊
Did he own a rainbow?
他是小组药师吗
Was he the group's pharmacist?
我们不太想谈
We don't like to talk about it.
可你们老谈
But you often do.
我专业就是解决问题的  给我点信息
I'm a problem solver give me information.
我来解决
I'll handle this.
特洛伊在钢鼓上非常有天赋
Troy was very gifted at steel drums.
钢鼓
Steel drums.
有意思
Interesting.
本次会议圆满成功
Well, this has been a great meeting.
我撤了
I'm off.
可能不会马上看到成果  但会有那么一天的
That won't pay off immediately, but it's gonna pay off.
杰夫  这就是真知
And that Jeff, is the truth.
■
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
你把藏了一块钱的蛋给整丢了吗
Did you lose the egg you put the dollar bill in?
还得藏吗
That's how it works?
翻  译    我们仍未知道那天手撕鬼子的那朵大菜
翻  译    在异世界认真打出拐弯子弹的蓬蓬裙
翻  译    老...老总...我......我DayDay想打鬼子!
翻  译    我可是要成为八路王的夕橙·撕物语
时 间 轴    某姜姜的超电磁三八大盖
后  期    秒撕五百鬼·鱼不能放弃骨头的理由
校对/总监  在地道战寻求邂逅是否搞错了什么
废柴联盟
第六季  第七集
布雷塔
Britta.
还记得你爱过的那个男人吗
Remember that guy you were in love with,
但你的爱被蹂躏粉碎
but your love was torn asunder
就因为他是公司拟人化后的三明治公民
because he was a human incarnation of certain sandwich franchise?
-赛百...  -别说出来
- Sub. - Don't say it.
没给钱不给他们打广告
Don't ever say that name without compensation.
我知道那段记忆对你来说有多痛苦
I know how much that experience hurt you,
所以我来给你提个醒
which is why I'm warning you
我刚刚在停车场看到他了
that I just saw him in the parking lot.
深呼吸  你体内的自毁倾向
Breathe, the self destructive part of you
正告诉你马上冲出去见他
wants to run straight to him,
但我要你明智起来  好吗
but you need to be smarter than that, right?
好的
Right.
谢谢你  安妮
Thank you Annie.
我还有堂课要去上
Now I have one more class,
如果你能等我四十分钟  我们在这
but if you can wait 40 minutes I will meet you.
我不是毫无准备就跑到野外的
See I just don't fling myself into the wild.
高质量的野外露营
The hub of a quality camping experience
全靠安全可靠发电机
is a safe and reliable generator.
过会我再跟你们聊  好吧
You know what I'll talk to you girls later, right.
坚持创造精神和热情
Stay inventive and enthusiastic.
谢谢
Thank you.
-布雷塔  -赛百...
- Britta. - Sub.
不不  那是我的三明治名
No, no, no, no, that's my sandwich name.
我现在是我自己
I'm my own man now.
我是一个自由可靠高质量的男人  我叫瑞克
I'm a free, reliable, quality man, named Rick.
你好  瑞克
Hi, Rick.
这是为我碎了一半的心
That's for half of my heart.
这是为我碎了另一半的心
And that's for the other half.
这是为我的心碎成两半的原因
And this is for being the reason there's two halves of my heart.
你蹲下点
Can you actually crouch down a little bit
因为我只练到黄带
cuz you're taller than my instructor
你比我教练高了点
and I'm only a yellow belt.
不  布雷塔
No, Britta
我用了那么长时间才重获自由
it took me this long to gain my freedom.
我一直都在想你
I never stopped thinking about you.
只有你才那么感动我
And you touched me in ways no one ever has.
说的漂亮
Nice.
我是为你回来的
I came back for you.
是吗
You did?
瑞克
Hey, Rick.
看我买什么了
Look what I got.
好啊  院长
Great Dean.
是啊
Yeah.
你的本田飞度呢
But where's your Honda Fit?
我开的是CR-V
Oh, I drive a CR-V.
是飞度结合了微型车的便利  可以更灵活地
The Fit combines the efficiency of a sub-compact
包容生活投向你的一切
with the versatility to take whatever life throws at you.
对啊  你就是那么说的
Yeah! That's what you said!
就是我啊
That's me!
CR-V也能包容生活投向我的一切吗
Can the CR-V not take what life throws at it?
能啊  但CR-V更耐用  空间更大
Yeah, but the CR-V has durability and storage.
好  也有道理
Okay, that makes sense.
我那家银行肯定有宽限期
I bet my bank has a grace period.
我要去买辆CR-V
I'm going to get a CR-V!
你是在给本田做游击营销吗
Are you guerrilla marketing for Honda?
你不应该知道的
You're not allowed to know that.
如果有人知道  我对本田就没有价值了
I'm useless to Honda, if anyone knows.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
又是旧戏重演
It's the same story all over again.
我反对
I disagree.
我觉得这是一个全新的故事
You know, I think it's a whole new story.
我现在留胡子了  还有身份
I have a beard now and an identity.
卖本田只是我的工作
Selling Hondas is just my job.
而且他们生产的好产品让我忍不住想去卖
And they make great products that I'd wanna sell, anyway.
那允许你交女朋友吗
So can you have a girlfriend?
我就知道
That's what I thought.
那就以后见了  朋友
Then, see you around as a friend.
作为朋友  布雷塔
As friend, Britta,
至少来看看这CR-V的
can I at least show you
可轻松折叠六四分隔可倒式后排座椅
the CR-V's easy fold-down 60-40 split row seat?
就十五分钟
For 15 minutes.
然后做真朋友
Then, friends for real.
好消息
Great news.
钢鼓的事儿有效果了吗
The steel drum thing paid off?
我们邀请了埃尔罗伊来自习室过游戏夜
We invited Elroy to meet us in the study room for a game night.
他答应了
He said, yes. Yeah!
你们是准备上演「求求你喜欢喜欢我们吧」
Are you gonna play pretty please, will you like us more?
他肯定感兴趣
That'll warm him up.
好戏在这  为庆祝埃尔罗伊在九十年代
Better. In celebration of Elroy's
所达到的人生高峰
life peaking in the early 90s,
猜耳朵
The Ears have it.
经典游戏  猜你有谁的耳朵  哪只耳朵
The classic game of whose ears you have, which ears have it,
你到底有没有耳朵
and whether you have those ears.
我们在研发新握手方法
We're work-shopping new hand shakes.
你们知道这样做只会加剧他的高冷吧
You guys realize it's just reinforcing his aloofness.
如果你想让别人喜欢你  别去了解他们
If you want someone to like you, you don't get to know them.
坐好  等着他们注意到你很酷
You sit back and wait for them to notice you're cool.
你这算啥  中二病
What are you? 13?
猜耳朵适用年龄是多少
What's the age allowance on The Ears Have It?
-七岁及以上  -那我就是六岁
- Seven and up. - Then I'm six.
我得说你确实更禁摩耐操了
I must say, you've become more reliable and durable.
希望我们可以再来一次
I hope we could do this again.
不行  瑞克  我想要正常的恋爱
No, Rick, I want a normal relationship.
我想能光明正大的去吃早午餐
I want to experience brunch in public.
我想给我父母发非要钱短信
I want a non-financial reason to text my parents.
我想指点另一个人怎么穿衣服
I want to tell another person how to dress.
我们可以成为男女朋友
We can have a relationship,
只不过要遵循几条简单的规定
we just have to follow a few simple rules.
瑞克
Rick?
你在里面吗
Are you in there?
你得躲起来
You have to hide.
车窗上都是雾
The windows are fogged over.
你是不是大睡了一觉
Are you napping heavily?
但我躲不了一世啊
I can't hide forever.
是  但你可以躲得舒舒服服的
No, but you can hide in comfort.
整个车舱空间高达35.2立方英尺
There's 35.2 cubic feet of cargo space back here.
求你了  布雷塔
Please, Britta.
该死
Dammit.
快来  快来  快来
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
本田本田  就选本田
Why choose, when you can Hond-oose.
那个鼓风机是我一时冲动买下的
Oh, and that blower that was just an impulse buy.
院长  一人只需一辆车就够了
Wow, Dean, you know, one vehicle's enough for one person.
我心里明白
I guess I know that in my head,
但我就是害怕
but I can't shake this fear
怕失去本田  一点点都不行
of losing even one small part of what Honda has to offer.
天啊  你是个七级易感体
My God, you're level seven susceptible.
-什么  -没什么  没什么
- What? - Nothing. Nothing, I-.
听我说  瑞克  你可以告诉我任何事
Look, Rick, whatever that is, you can tell me.
我和你一边的
I'm on board.
好
Yes.
是啊
Yes, you are.
我生活在非洲吗
Am I found in Africa?
对  还有圣地亚哥  纽约布朗克区
Yes, and San Diego, and the Bronx.
是女人吗
A woman?
我是不是很大
Am I large?
我是不是大象
Am I elepant?
我本来想的是海豚
I was thinking dolphin,
但我知道海豚没耳朵
but I knew they didn't have ears
因为我的牙医在天花板上贴了一张海豚的图
because my dentist has a poster of one on the ceiling,
而我最近才做了牙根管手术
and I recently had a root canal.
大伙儿们  走廊那头都能听到你们笑声了
Hey, party people, I could hear you all the way down the hall.
我们在玩猜耳朵  昌已经领先三副了
We're playing The Ears Have it, Chang's ahead by three pair.
有待讨论
With an asterisk.
我作弊了
I'm cheating.
你坐我这儿吧
Hey, you can have my spot.
我该走了
I should, I should leave.
别啊  和你一起玩很开心  埃尔罗伊
Oh, no, well, fun hanging out with you Elroy.
你有选择朋友的权利
We know you have your choice of friends
谢谢你选择了我们
and we thank you for choosing us.
这还不好选吗
Easy choice to make.
看见了吧  早说了
See, told ya.
埃尔罗伊不喜欢我们  这可怎么办呢
Elroy doesn't like us, what are we gonna do?
你们真是呆瓜
You guys are goofs.
是啊  我们太蠢了
Yeah, we were silly.
我要去做干酪玉米片
I got up to make nachos
埃尔罗伊说  我来干[谐音]
and Elroy said, that was not-cho job.
笑死我们了
And we laughed.
然后他就真的给我们做了
Then he made them for me.
他不是和我们玩文字游戏
It was more than word play.
他是真心想要做给我们的
It really wasn't my job in his eyes.
今天我才看见他这样的一面
I hadn't seen that side of him until now.
他和我们在一起很开心
He had a great time.
直到杰夫出现
Till Jeff showed up.
也许他只是不喜欢杰夫
Maybe he just doesn't like Jeff.
好  到我了
Okay, my deal.
波士顿玩法
Boston rules.
一张上  一张下
Two up, one down.
精灵的耳朵是大的  小丑的耳朵正常
Elf ears are wild, joker ears are regular ears.
耳朵离开头就作废
Ears go cold once they're off the head.
老鼠耳朵算自动认输
Rat ears are an automatic loss.
不许偷看  用鼻子嗅  或打呼呼
No sneaking, sniffing, or grunting,
也不许问我有没有耳垂
and no asking do I have lobes.
目前昌领先三副牌
Chang's ahead by three pair.
有待讨论
With an asterisk.
你们瞎说
It's not true, you know.
是真的  我什么都作弊
Oh, it is. I cheat my ass off at everything.
这种躲猫猫的游戏我也要作弊
I'm cheating at a game of hide and seek right now.
谁都别想离开这里了
We weren't supposed to leave the rec center.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
好了  开始吧
Okay, let's do this.
额外卡
Extra cards.
该死的水池
Stupid sink!
次次如此
Every time!
喵的
Mother.
我恨你
I hate.
不着急
No rush.
想要来点什么
What do you need?
一杯汽水  谢谢
A club soda please.
不如加点料吧
How about a little something in there to keep it company?
有什么推荐的
What do you recommend?
威士忌加汽水可是经典
Well, scotch and soda's is a classic.
这瓶就不错
This one's okay.
这瓶是刚进的
We just got this one in.
但瓶子上有头猪
It's got a pig on the bottle.
这瓶  这瓶才是极品
But this one, this one's really good.
八年发酵
Aged eight years.
口感醇厚
Smoky.
苏格兰进口
From Scotland.
价格高点  但绝对值
A little pricier but worth it.
有开心事要庆祝的时候  我就来点这个
I drink this one when I've got a reason to celebrate.
那就这个吧
Then I will take that one.
今天是有开心事要庆祝
I think I've got something to celebrate.
是吗  什么开心事
Oh, yeah, what's that?
她很厉害
She's good.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
布雷塔  这是我的上司
Britta, this is my boss.
本田的
From Honda?
现在开始  你就是我们公司的希拉里了
In public you'll refer to us as Hilary from now on.
接着说
Continue.
我们可以参与一个项目
There's a program we can be in,
组成一个隐性团队
where we covertly market as a team,
我们可以成为公开的情侣
we can be a couple in a relationship in public.
在大庭广众下手牵手
We can walk down the street holding hands.
条件我是接受这份工作
If I take a job tricking people
诱使人们购买他们并不需要的东西
into buying things they don't want.
你喜欢广告牌和广告吗  派利小姐
Do you enjoy billboards and commercials, Miss Perry?
你是说那些广骗牌和欺诈片吗
You mean shill-boards and con-mercials?
不喜欢
No, I don't.
我也讨厌
I detest them.
它们就像不守规矩的推土车
They are unmanned bulldozers
所到之处  欺蒙拐骗
rolling over everything in their path.
但瑞克的工作就像医生
What Rick does is surgical.
他发现本田可以帮助改善生活中的不如意
He finds that part of each life that Honda can improve
并将这些不如意通过最有效的信息解决
and gently bathes it in the most helpful information possible.
这和医生的工作不太一样吧
I don't think, you understand how surgery works.
我进来只点了一份汽水
I came in here to get a club soda.
现在我却喝上了
Right now, I am drinking probably,
多年来尝过的最醇美的威士忌
the best Scotch I've had in years.
你耍了我吗
Did you trick me?
我受到伤害了吗
Am I suffering?
你爱这个男人吗
Do you love this man?
-爱  -那现在起你们就是广告情侣了
- I do. - Then I pronounce you a highly influential couple.
你可以亲吻男票了
You may kiss your boyfriend.
等等  他哪儿去了
Wait, where'd he go?
我们不用弄明白
Whoa, that's not for us to understand.
好吧  可他就在那儿呢
Well, okay, but he's right there.
你好  托德
Hi, Todd.
好啊
Hey guys.
能坐这儿吗
Mind if we sit with you?
好啊  太好了
Oh, yeah, that would be great.
不得不说  你们看起来太幸福了
I have to say, you guys seem very happy together.
我们爱上了彼此
Hm, we have our moments.
这周末我们还有一起逛古董呢  好开心哦
I'm excited because we're going antiquing this weekend.
我喜欢逛古董
I love antiquing.
全都旧旧的
Everything is so old.
我也喜欢
I like it too.
你不是不喜欢的嘛
You said you hated it.
我讨厌的是找到的古董
I hated finding these treasures
放不到我们车里
and not being able fit them in the car.
现在我有本田CR-V了
Now I got a CR-V.
-CR-V  -对  瑞克的新本田
- CR-V? - Yeah, Rick's new Honda.
天天就念叨这个
He won't shut up about it.
整个生活都因它改变了
Yeah, it's kind of a game changer.
性福指数也大大提高了
Certainly a sex life changer!
别这么口无遮拦嘛
Sorry, for being obnoxious!
你最近忙什么呢
So what you've been up to?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
是CR-V吗
CR-V you say?
CR-V
CR-V.
你简直神了
You're amazing.
你才神了
本田神了
Honda's amazing.
我要把你介绍给我爸妈
I want you to meet my parents.
好啊
Yes.
本田
Honda.
-布雷塔陷入爱河了  -是啊
- Look, Britta's in love.   - Yup.
他一定是个特别的小伙子
He must be a very special young man.
我想这段感情一定会长久的
I bet they'll be together for a very long time.
你唬到他了  妥妥的
Man you got him pegged, man, pegged.
杰夫
Hey Jeff.
你坐我的位子吧
Hey, here you can have my seat.
我得去上课了
I'm just going to class.
等等  我还有事要告诉你
Oh, wait, before you go,
我知道「冰冻娜塔莉」的每张专辑你都有了
I know you have every one of Natalie's Freezing CDs,
不过阿布蒂在网上找到一张
but Abed found some songs by them online
他们为无家可归的滑板运动员做的慈善专辑
that they did for a charity album for homeless skateboarders.
「塑料娃娃零件」「墙纸蛹」「古怪毯子」
Plastic doll parts, wall paper chrysalis, weird blanket.
这几首我都没听过
I never heard these.
太棒了  谢谢
This is great, thanks.
远离那个机械师
Stay away from that mechanic.
除非我需要甘草扳子
Unless I need wrench made of licorice.
上帝啊  抱歉
Oh, man, I'm, I'm sorry.
天啊  我对他就像个屁
Man, I'm like a fart to that guy.
他一见我真是闪得够快
He can't get away fast enough.
什么  哪有  其实有一点吧
What? No, I mean, maybe.
之前玩猜耳朵的时候搞什么鬼了
What the hell happened at that ears game
他怎么会那么喜欢你们
that made him like you so much?
只是人性脆弱的一些小时光
A few brief moments of human vulnerability.
真的不是你能掌控的
Not really your wheelhouse.
我看你对这个人性的弱点
Oh, I'm sure you have detailed files
倒是了解得很嘛  阿布蒂
on human vulnerability, Abed.
退让一步吧  哥儿们
Whoa, take a knee, man.
他说的没错  杰夫
He's right, Jeff.
如果你想要埃尔罗伊喜欢你
If you want Elroy to like you,
也许你得敞开心扉
maybe you need to put yourself out there.
你是说要收买他吗
You mean bribe him?
买个小礼物
With gifts?
比如你的「娜塔沙冰冰」CD
Like your Natasha Freezes CD?
是「冰冻娜塔莉」乐队
Natalie's Freezing.
冰冻娜塔莉
Natalie is freezing.
冰冻娜塔莉  冰你妹
Natalie is freezing. Natalie is freezing.
搞什么
What is this?
我不知道  我...
I don't know, I.
我也不知道
I don't know.
本田
Honda.
梦想的力量
The power of dreams.
派尔顿院长  我知道你经不起广告的诱惑
Dean Pelton, I know how susceptible you are to advertising.
你是不是也要说我是七级易感体
Would you say, I'm a level seven susceptible.
当然不是  我干嘛这么说你
No, because why would I?
这种话是月球人说的
Because that's moon man talk.
你之前提到一个新来的孩子
You mentioned a new kid earlier,
就是那个跟你讨论本田飞度的
who told you about the new Honda Fit.
-瑞克  -布雷塔的男友吗
- Rick.  - Britta's boyfriend?
对  但不是他
Yeah, but he's not.
不是
No.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
他才不会偷偷给本田打工呢
And he wouldn't secretly be working for Honda,
因为我刚认识他的时候
because when we first met
他是在偷偷给另外一家公司打工
he was secretly working for completely different company.
你...我不知道怎么说
Are you... I don't know how to...
有一个规定要求我要有建设性
I have a rule about being constructive,
所以我现在不能问任何问题
so I can't ask any questions right now.
因为我现在想问的问题都带有修辞
Because all of the questions I have right now are rhetorical
而且问完都很蠢
and they end with the word idiot.
你知道啥是修辞吗
Do you know what a rhetorical...
哦  你当然不知道了
No, of course you don't know what that is,
你本身就很蠢
you're an idiot.
对不起  太  对  不  起  了
I'm sorry, I am so sorry.
不过你那么蠢
But you're so stupid.
你根本不知道的吧
You have no idea.
而且你就是绝无仅有的没头脑  知道为啥吗
And you're the only one who has no idea, because guess why?
千万别回答我  你一定是错的
Don't answer that, you'll get it wrong.
你个小傻瓜
So dumb.
你就是个每分每秒都想毁了学校的
You're just a dumb little man who tries to destroy this school
小傻逼
every minute.
对不起
I am sorry.
我又对不起了
I'm so sorry.
好了好了没事了
Oh it's okay.
其实还有事  但是...
I mean it's not okay, but shh, shh, shh.
唉  太蠢了你
Oh, so stupid.
哦  乖
Oh shh, shh, shh.
真是个小傻逼
Such a dummy.
你带个朋友来我们真是太高兴了
We are just so thrilled that you brought a friend.
高兴
Thrilled.
这位是你带回来的朋友吗
And, and it is friend then?
这么叫真的准确吗
I mean is that the correct moniker?
-是男朋友  -这就对啦
- Boyfriend.  - Hello.
就对味儿啦
This is, well that's, whoa, this is very exciting.
小子  你拿下了我的另一个小甜心啊
Boy you could just bowl me over with one of those sweet heart,
你还记得我们在约翰逊的小船屋里吗
you know what are the, you remember at the Johnson's cabin, we.
羽毛
Feathers.
你用羽毛就能把我拿下
You could blow me over with a feather.
您家真棒
Well, you have a lovely home.
我喜欢这个地毯
I love this carpet.
让我想起我的本田CR-V的高质量地毯垫
It reminds me of the quality floor mats in my Honda CR-V.
亲爱的这个现在真的不重要
Oh, come on sweetie that's not necessary.
你提到了地毯垫的高品质
You refer to your floor mats as quality,
我还从来没见过谁对地毯垫有那么高的热情
I've never heard that level of floor mat enthusiasm.
我们是不是也该关心关心
Should we be caring more
自家的地毯呀  乔治
about our floor mats, George?
别那么快下结论  小黛
I don't think we should jump to conclusions, Deb.
让他把话说完
Just let the man finish his story.
就是地毯垫
They're floor mats.
没了  说完了
That's the story.
哎哟  这是啥呀
Hey, what's this?
那又是啥  四处看看
What's that? Look all around.
我们身边啥都有哈
There's things all around us.
你想看电影吗
Would you like to see a movie?
我们有一部  叫什么来着  乔治
We have one. What is it, George?
阿瓦达飞行员
It's it's the The Aviator.
不对  是阿凡达
No, no, it, The Avatar.
算了  那货就是三小时长的裹脚布
No thank you, that movie is three hours of puke.
当然啦  布雷塔在开玩笑呢
Of course, Britta's joking.
我们当然喜欢看阿凡达啦
We enjoy Avatar very much.
是吗
We do?
是啊  这电影超火的
Yes, it's an immensely popular movie.
我们当然喜欢
Of course, we love it.
有多少校友回应了
How many alumni have responded?
不是很多
Not many.
不过我觉得我们现有的学生
But I think our current students
为了学分也会来的
will show up for the degree raffle.
我们把DJ放那边好不好
How about we put the DJ over there?
你们用不着DJ了
You're not gonna need a DJ.
自从随机播放键被发明以来我就一直这么说
I've been saying that since the invention of the shuffle button.
今晚我预约了一位让你们惊喜的音乐人
I have booked a surprise musical guest this evening.
带点90年代乡愁风的
A little piece of 90s nostalgia
「冰冻娜塔莉」乐队
you might call Natalie is Freezing.
你脑子烧了吧
Are you out of your damn mind.
啥  你也知道这个乐队吗
What? You know this band?
废话  我当然知道
You know damn well I do.
你到底想干嘛
Why do you always wha, what,
想让我喜欢你吗
what, are you trying to get me to like you?
-才没有  -那就好  我才不会喜欢你
- No. - Good, cuz it aint' working.
你个怪胎  发胶男  心肺复苏假人
You weird, hair gelled, CPR dummy.
那是发蜡好吗
It's pomade.
我站那么高有人想让我帮忙拿点什么吗
As long as I'm up here, does anyone want anything reached?
大家好  我们是「冰冻娜塔莉」乐队
Hey, we're Natalie is Freezing.
你就是娜塔莉吗
Oh, are you Natalie?
我叫茱莉  我们乐队名叫「冰冻娜塔莉」
I'm Julie. The name of the band is Natalie is Freezing.
为什么非得乐队成员有人叫娜塔莉
Why would anyone in the band be Natalie?
我们是搞艺术的
We're artists.
不错嘛
Cool.
我们的DJ要去操作冻酸奶机的
So, our DJ was going to man the frozen yogurt machine.
那种东西你们搞得定吗
Is that something you guys can handle?
你们要这个动作伴舞吗  我练了很久了
If you do need anything reached, I've been practicing.
你说我们喜欢阿凡达
We like Avatar?
对外来说  是的
In public, yes.
我们喜欢大众所爱
We like things most people like.
我们的工作不是要脱离群众
Our job isn't to alienate people.
在我父母面前我们还搞上班这套吗
We're on the job with my parents?
无差别面对全人类  全世界  全宇宙
With everyone, everywhere, all the time.
你不是要恋爱关系吗
You wanted a relationship.
我要的是真的
A real one.
这就是真的
It's real.
你不相信本田能做出好产品吗
Do you not think, Honda makes good products?
我当然相信
Of course, I do.
这个我从来不怀疑
That's never been remotely in question.
但你说我喜欢阿凡达又是几个意思
But, why does that mean that I like Avatar?
因为你不是非主流
Because you're not a monster.
好吗  因为人家不想跟非主流开一样的车
Right, cuz people don't want to drive what a monster drives.
别再跟我说本田了  瑞克
Stop the Honda, Rick.
听到我说的了吗
Do you hear me?
用你的脚轻触这个神奇汽车的
Use a light press of your foot engage the highly responsive
高敏感度防锁制动装置  马上
anti lock brakes of this incredible vehicle, now.
我是想和你在一起的  我要真实的你
I want to be with you, the real you.
这就是真实的我
This is me.
我就是这样的
This is what I do.
当我感化别人买本田产品的时候
When I influence people to buy Honda products,
我能感受到上帝般的愉悦
I feel God's pleasure.
这是「火之战车」的台词
That's from Chariots of Fire.
我喜欢看「火之战车」
I love Chariots of Fire.
我也是
So do I.
当然我们也必须去喜欢
Also we have to.
去你的  布雷塔
Dammit Britta.
不是吧
Oh man.
你们这群人怎么阴魂不散
You people are everywhere.
想找个地方躲都不行
I was looking for a place to hide.
不用担心  我才不会烦你
Don't worry, I'm not gonna bother you.
那好吧  给我来杯金汤力
Okay then, give me a gin and tonic.
你朋友杰夫给舞会订到了「冰冻娜塔莉」乐队
Your friend Jeff booked Natalie is Freezing for the dance.
什么
What?
今晚吗  那我们得去啊
Tonight? We gotta go.
你怎么都不开心啊
Why aren't you excited?
我之前约过她
I used to date her.
不是吧
Really.
她叫茱莉
Her name is Julie.
为什么乐队名非得用她的名字
Why would the bands name be her name?
她是个艺术家
She's an artist.
我们都一起听过她的歌
We've listened to them together.
你从来没提过
You never said anything about this.
她耍了我  她曾耍得我死去活来
She messed me up, she messed me up pretty good.
来这里就是为了遗忘的
Here's to forgetting.
我才不要敬这个
Not gonna toast to that.
那也忘了你吧
Well, then forget you too.
少来了你
Give me a break.
这就是问题所在
That's the whole problem.
所有人在那么一瞬间都会选择自保的
Everybody's in such a rush to protect themselves from each other.
当然  你要守卫自己的城堡  但也得
Sure. Yes, you gotta defend your castle, but you also gotta.
城堡里的那玩意儿叫啥来着
What's that thing that castles have?
城墙
Walls.
-别闹  -护城河
- Come on. - A moat.
过了护城河  过了护城河
It goes over the moat, goes over the moat.
敌军骑士  骑兵之箭
Enemy knights, cavalry arrows?
不是啦  不是
No, come on. Stop it.
就像这样儿的
It goes like this.
鳄鱼
Alligators?
不是  就是一种东西
No, it's one thing.
一种机械装置
It's mechanical.
一条机械鳄鱼
One mechanical alligator?
你是不是在耍我
Are you screwing with me?
我根本不晓得你在说什么
I don't even know what the hell you're talking about.
就是一种机械玩意儿啦
It's one mechanical thing.
越过护城河的那个
It goes over the moat.
像这样这样的
It goes like this.
投石车
A catapult!
吓死人了  你发什么疯
Oh, Jesus! What, what are you doing?
布雷塔
Britta.
我爱你
I love you.
我要从本田公司辞职了
I'm gonna quit Honda.
我会去找工作  我不晓得
I'll get a job I, I, I don't know.
正常人都怎么做
What do regular people do?
哦对  他们会买东西
Well they buy things.
我会去做的
I'll do that.
为了我吗
For me?
不  为了本田  当然是为你
No, for Honda. Yes, for you.
通常呢我会折磨一下你
Normally I would give you a hard time,
但我不想变得像这个人一样
but I don't wanna be like this guy.
你要过来吗
Wait you're coming.
-我要过去  -你过来吗
- I'm coming to you. - You're coming over?
行  要不要
Okay. Do you?
貌似你迈得相当艰难啊
Okay that seems like really the hard way.
小心桌上有条缝
Okay wait watch out for the split there.
-好  -抱紧
- Okay. - Hold on.
抱紧我
Hold on to me!
我的天
Oh my God.
现在我们要做什么
Oh, wow what do we do now?
我们学校今晚有舞会
My school's having a dance tonight.
我最爱的乐队会来演出
My favorite band is playing.
-走吧  -好
- Let's go! - Okay!
吊桥  是吊桥
A drawbridge, a drawbridge.
你要的是一座吊桥
You need a drawbridge.
也是埃尔罗伊最喜欢的乐队
It's Elroy's favorite band too.
我曾经在幻觉中看到他房车里有一张乐队MV
I once, I once hallucinated one of their music videos in his RV.
好奇怪哦
That's weird.
不行  院长今晚没办法介绍乐队出场
No, the Dean can't introduce the band tonight.
他正在办公室苦苦思索该为体育部
He's in his office deciding what kind of vehicles to buy
买哪种车呢
for the athletic department.
对  他需要一整队
Yeah, he needs a whole fleet.
没错  一整队车
That's right a fleet of vehicles.
他只是需要选一个车型  就在他办公室
He just needs to pick a model of car. He's in his office.
-你有没有听到  -我听到了
- Did you hear that? - Yes, I heard it,
瑞克  但我们已经退出了
Rick, but we're out of the game.
还没
Not yet.
我们可以以高业绩的姿态离开
We can leave on a high.
院长可是属于七级易感体  布雷塔
The Dean is a level seven susceptible, Britta.
这是一种千载难逢的感觉  你不会相信的
It's a one-in-a-lifetime feeling, you won't believe it.
我相信  但我不需要
I do believe it, but I don't need it.
你需要吗
Do you?
我只要完成这最后一份工作
I'll just do this one last job,
然后我们就自由了
then we'll be free.
我马上回来
Be right back.
我想我也是七级易感体吧
Guess I'm a level seven susceptible too.
为什么他们会以为乐队里有叫娜塔莉的人
Why do they assume somebody is named Natalie in the band?
好像一直都会这样
It, it like happens all the time.
还记得咱们在锡拉丘兹的时候吗
Like, remember we were in Syracuse?
埃尔罗伊
Elroy?
茱莉  你真是耍惨我了
Julie, you messed me up.
你因为我不感兴趣所以来追我
You came after me because I wasn't interested.
你勾起我的兴趣  我爱上你了
You got me interested, and I fell hard.
你又觉得无聊  把我整崩溃了
Then you got bored and destroyed me.
从那时起长达二十年我害怕爱上任何人
And I've been afraid to love anybody for 20 years since,
但现在不会了
but not anymore.
-好吧  -我还爱你
- Okay. - I still love you,
但我不会因为你伤害了我
but I'm not gonna keep on hurting others,
而再去伤害别人
just because you hurt me.
行吧
Fine.
行啊
这就是你  这就是你给我的印象
That's you. That's my impression of you,
你这个一脸厌倦的嬉皮废柴
you jaded hipster a-hole.
我依然爱你的音乐
I still love your music.
祝演出成功
Have a great gig.
埃尔罗伊  我厌倦了这游戏
Elroy, I'm tired of playing this game.
我喜欢你  我也想让你喜欢我
I like you and I want you to like me.
好
Okay.
你是个好青年  杰夫·翁格
You're a good guy, Jeff Winger.
你和我会成为朋友的
You and I are gonna be friends.
好吧  挺好的
Okay, great, whatever.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你  我爱你  我爱你
I love you. I love you. I love you.
我爱你  我爱你
I love you. I love you.
对不起  布雷塔
Sorry, Britta.
布雷塔  你知不知道你男朋友
Britta, did you know your boyfriend
在为本田做游击营销
was guerrilla marketing for Honda?
我知道他代表了某种我想买的品牌
I knew he represented something I wanted to buy.
我做得好吧  弗兰
I did good, Frankie.
我做的好不好
Didn't I do good?
好  乖院长
Yes, good Dean.
院长好聪明哦
Smart Dean.
他会没事的
He'll be fine.
但他永远也不能再回这里了
But he can never come back here.
我知道
I understand.
当然  如果你愿意加入我们的话
Of course if, you want to come with us.
因为你很优秀
Because you are good.
我其实什么都没做
I had nothing to do with it.
2015本田CR-V本身就意味着畅销
The 2015 Honda CR-V sells itself.
所以今年正是运动型多用途车的大趋势之年
That's why it's this years Motor Trend Sport Utility of the Year.
天哪  他去哪儿了
Oh my, where did he go?
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道大家都知道下首歌
I know all of you know this next one.
是「垃圾」
Garbage woo hoo!
*月光  流血的玻璃  疗伤的针*
* Moonlight, bleeding glass and healing needles, *
*切掉的心脏再也不完整*
* amputated hearts are never whole. *
我想这首歌是写给我的
I think this song is about me.
*太皎洁*
* Too bright. *
或是海洛因  管他呢
Or heroin. Who cares?
*在梦中  尖叫的海鸥*
* Dreaming as the screaming seagulls *
*啄食了水下的我*
* feed on parts of me I keep below, oh, oh, *
*猎户座  解下你的腰带*
* Orion, take off your belt *
*带我去向你的所在*
* and let me go where you've been. *
*我自由翱翔越过内心已死的水牛*
* I'm flying overhead the buffalo are falling dead inside. *
*你我永垂不朽*
* Eternity it was you and me, *
*无比甜蜜  我的游星*
how sweet it'd be, my wandering star. *
现在我要问问题了
So now I ask a question.
妈妈问  我们答
Mom does, we answer it.
我是啥
What am I?
-兔子  -你不能这么做
- A rabbit. - Obviously you can't do that,
你不能问自己是什么
obviously you can't ask what you are.
-妈妈  换耳朵  -好呀  乖乖
- Mom, change your ears. - Okay, sweetie.
你之前也没说这个呀
Well, you didn't say that before.
爸  问妈一个关于你耳朵的问题
Dad, ask Mom a question about your ears.
我又看不到自己的耳朵
I can't see my ears.
所以才要你问啊
That's why you're asking.
好吧  小黛  我的耳朵是啥
Okay. Deb, what are my ears?
错  应该是  我是动物吗
No. Like, am I an animal?
对
Well, yes.
你是  你也是
You are, and so are you.
布雷塔  瑞克怎么了
Britta, whatever happened to Rick?
-我的天  -好啦好啦
- Oh my God. - Okay, okay.
我想你们不过是露水情缘吧
Ships in the night I guess.
你干吗要问啊
Why would you ask that?
我来这里就是因为我和瑞克分手了
I came over here, because Rick and I broke up.
我知道  我以为也许有所改变呢
I know that. I just thought maybe something had changed.
我坐在这儿就改变了吗
While I was sitting here?
你也知道那段玩尽天下App的日子
Well you know these days with all the apps.
玩游戏啦
Play the game.
好吧  咱们的哪个朋友会收集我
All right, which friend of ours collects me?
乔安·斯库巴克
Joann Schunbucker.
我是大象
I'm elephant.
对啦
Yes.
你们是怎么做到的
How in the hell did you-.
-我是动物吗  -绝对不是
- Am I an animal? - Not by a long shot.
我在你办公室工作吗
Do I work in your office?
妈
Mom.
内森  应收帐户
Nathan, in accounts receivable,
非原配  而是第二任妻子
not his first wife but second wife,
阵亡将士纪念日做蛋糕的那个
the one that made cake for Memorial Day.
我是不是史波克
Am I Mr Spock.
没错  你是  我喜欢这个游戏
Yes you are, I love this game.
-我知道  -好好玩
- I know. - This is fun.
我想我们哪里又做错了
I think we did something wrong.
我知道的  小黛
I know we did, Deb.
■
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧
■
你看懂了吗
Did you get any of that?